Shakur Miro

Franklin, NH

720-707-8361

miiro.shakur@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a position that will utilize, help me learn and improve my skills do good for people that need caring in nursing.

SUMMARY OF SKILLS:

Experienced LPN with over four years of experience in Ventilator, wound care, Trach care, G-tubes, PEG tube, NG-Tubes in settings like homes and nursing facilities.

Trained in clear and detailed nursing documentation which I believe is the cornerstone for better continuous care.

Good English skills excellent reading and writing skills in English Reliable and responsible Strong computer skills (Internet, Microsoft word, email)

EDUCATION:

University of District Of Colombia, Washington, D.C –L.P. N/L.V.N program, October 2010-October 2011.

RELATED EXPERIENCE:

Team Manager

Canadian Red Cross, Toronto, ON, Canada

FEBRUARY 2009-JUNE 2010

Volunteered and led a team of five attendees to welcome and provide hospitality to shelter and relief seekers.

Managed a variety of clients' accounts

Team manager

Canadian Feed the Children, Toronto, ON, Canada

Volunteered and lead a team of two associates to attain and maintain donors for different relief programs.

Trained clinical and geriatrics nursing practice Hadley Hospital, Washington, D.C October 2010-october 2011

Practiced L.P.N acute and geriatric care with the guide of an extremely experienced Nursing instructor.

Learned to do full body assessments.

Trained to perform top quality wound care.

Taught to meticulously deliver prescribed medication doses to identified clients.

Took turns to lead designated teams

Trained in proper nursing documentation.

Trained to practice at a high standard as expected by future employees.

Mental Health Nursing Care Training
ST. Elizabeth Hospital
Practiced L.P.N acute and geriatric care with the guidance of an extremely experienced Nursing instructor

Trained in exquisite neurological assessment.

Trained to promptly administer prescribed medications.

Trained in proper nursing documentation.

MEDICAL SURGICAL AND SUB ACUTE CARE TRAINING. HOWARD HOSPITAL

Practiced L.P.N acute care for all different age groups with the guidance of an extremely experienced Nursing instructor.

Provided pre-operative and post-operative care. Provided diverse care like tracheostomy care, I.V site care Administered prescribed medications.

CHARGE NURSE/NURSE SUPERVISOR.

NMS HEALHTCARE NURSING AND REHAB: 12/12 -05/13

Medication administration as ordered by physicians.

Tracheostomy and Ventilator patient management and nursing care.

GNA supervision and monitoring.

Supervise nursing staff during day and evening shifts.

Monitor lab results and notify physicians as ordered.

Update residents' care plans.

Assess and assist with admissions.

Very much experience and trained staff with the use of various wound vacs.

LPN NURSE

BRIGHT STAR HOMEHEALTH CARE 06/13 to 11/13

Provided medication management Vent, Trach and wound care to female client who was diagnosed with Muscular dystrophy.

Help to provide updates and education to husband and family about POC.

CASE MANAGER/CLINICAL CO-ORDINATOR.

NMS HEALTHCARE NURSING AND REHAB: 06/13 - 02/14

Verify insurance benefits for referrals/possible admissions.

Review clinicals for referrals/possible admission and make sure we facility can provided required services.

Attain authorization from insurance companies for patients' admission.

Review and fax required weekly clinical updates to residents' insurance case managers and medical directors.

Schedule recommended appointments with out of facility clinicians.

Work with various departments to schedule and plan safe discharge.

Facility marketing to out of state hospitals and institutions.

CLINICAL LIAISON

NMS HEALTHCARE 03/14 to 12/15

Worked to build relationships between the facility and hospital social workers.

Checked and verified clinical conditions prior to admission to make sure the facility can provide the needed care.

Worked with DON and VP of clinical services to update needed clinical policies in relation to the admission processes.

TRAVEL NURSE

INTEGRATED HEALTHCARE STAFFING 01/16 to 11/16

Worked as a nurse in various facilities on behalf of the company. I simply helped in augmentation of different staff members in various facilities all over the state of Colorado and especially had to learn various documentation systems/platforms.

LPN NURSE

ADVANCED HOME CARE 03/17 to present

Worked every Saturday, Sunday, Monday and Thursday 7pm to 7am with a male client who is a quadriplegic since his occupational accident in 2012.

Client is provided with Vent care, Trach care and wound care.

Monitor client and review medications with supervisor on a monthly basis.

Travelling Nurse

National Staffing Solutions

November 2018-Present

Currently working as a charge nurse in a skilled nursing facility in Franklin, NH for 40hrs/week including every other weekend.

September 2019-present

Started attending UNH-coding class with in-class experience and completed project with Javascript, HTML, CSS, Jquery, and Node. js.